<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name_3">License_Project_2</string>

    <string name="SectionOneTheoryDef_3">‚Ä¢ Power with a Natural Exponent:
    \n ‚ó¶ Definition: For a rational number a and a natural number n ‚â• 2, the power a‚Åø is the product of n factors, each equal to a. a¬π is defined to be a.
    \n ‚ó¶ Terminology: In a‚Åø, a is the base, n is the exponent, and the result a‚Åø is the power. Special names include a¬≤ (square) and a¬≥ (cube).

       \n ‚Ä¢ Taking the Root (Evolution):
    \n ‚ó¶ Definition: Evolution is the inverse operation of involution. The nth root of a number a (where n ‚â• 2) is a number which, when raised to the nth power, produces a.
    \n ‚ó¶ Notation: The nth root is symbolized as ‚Åø‚àöa, where n is the index of the root and a is the integrand. For n=2 (square root), the index is usually omitted (‚àöa). The third root is called the cube root.
</string>
    <string name="SectionOneTheoryProperties_3">‚Ä¢ Power with a Natural Exponent, properties: \n
    1. An even power of a negative number is positive.
        \n 2. An odd power of a negative number is negative.
        \n 3. Any power of a positive number is positive.
        \n 4. Raising zero to any natural exponent results in zero (0‚Åø = 0).
        \n 5. Raising unity to any natural exponent results in unity (1‚Åø = 1).

    \n ‚Ä¢ Taking the Root (Evolution), properties:
        \n ‚ó¶ Existence: Taking the root is not always possible within the set of rational numbers. For instance, ‚àö2 is not a rational number, a fact proven by contradiction in the text.
    \n ‚ó¶ Approximate Roots: While exact roots of any rational number may not exist, approximate values always do. An approximate value b of ‚Åø‚àöa (with deficit and accuracy Œ±) satisfies b‚Åø &lt; a &lt; (b + Œ±)‚Åø. The text provides examples of finding approximate square roots.</string>
    <string name="SectionOneTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionOneQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>


    <string name="SectionTwoTheoryDef_3">‚Ä¢ Definition:
    ‚ó¶ An irrational number is represented by a nonterminating, nonperiodic decimal of the form a = c.b‚ÇÅb‚ÇÇb‚ÇÉ....
    ‚ó¶ Every positive irrational number has a corresponding negative irrational number.
    ‚ó¶ Two irrational numbers are considered equal if their integer parts and all corresponding decimal digits are equal.
</string>
    <string name="SectionTwoTheoryProperties_3">‚Ä¢ Origin of Irrational Numbers: The process of taking roots can result in nonterminating, nonperiodic decimal fractions. For example, the decimal representation of ‚àö2 begins 1.41421... and is not periodic, which was proven in the preceding section. These non-repeating, non-ending decimals define a new type of number.
    \n‚Ä¢ Comparing Irrational Numbers: The comparison of two positive irrational numbers is done by comparing their integer parts and then their decimal digits sequentially. To compare an irrational number with a rational one, the rational number is represented as a periodic decimal.
\n‚Ä¢ Examples:
    \n‚ó¶ Roots of natural numbers that are not perfect squares (e.g., ‚àö2, ‚àö3, ‚àö5) are irrational.
    \n‚ó¶ The number œÄ (pi), the ratio of a circle's circumference to its diameter, is an irrational number (approximately 3.14...).
    \n‚ó¶ Values of logarithms and trigonometric functions are also often irrational.</string>
    <string name="SectionTwoTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionTwoQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionThreeTheoryDef_3">‚Ä¢ Real Numbers:
    \n ‚ó¶ The union of the set of rational and irrational numbers forms the set of real numbers.
    \n ‚ó¶ A real number is either rational (represented by a terminating or periodic decimal) or irrational (represented by a nonperiodic decimal).
    \n ‚ó¶ The basic properties of arithmetic operations (commutative, associative, distributive) defined for whole numbers also hold for real numbers.
    \n ‚ó¶ Operations on irrational numbers can lead to either rational or irrational results. For example, (5 + ‚àö2) - ‚àö2 = 5 (rational), but the sum or product of a rational and an irrational number is always irrational (if the rational number is not zero).
\n ‚Ä¢ Arithmetical nth Root:
    \n ‚ó¶ Definition: The arithmetical nth root of a non-negative number a is the non-negative number b for which b‚Åø = a. This definition is only for non-negative values of a.
    \n ‚ó¶ Uniqueness: For any a ‚â• 0, the arithmetical root ‚Åø‚àöa exists and is unique.
    \n ‚ó¶ Modulus: The basic properties of the modulus (absolute value) extend from rational numbers to all real numbers.
\n ‚Ä¢ Rectangular Coordinates (Cartesian Plane):
    \n ‚ó¶ The plane is defined by two mutually perpendicular number lines, the x-axis (horizontal axis of abscissas) and the y-axis (vertical axis of ordinates), which intersect at the origin O(0,0).
    \n ‚ó¶ These axes divide the plane into four quadrants.
    \n ‚ó¶ Coordinates: Any point M in the plane corresponds to a unique ordered pair of numbers (x, y), its coordinates. The abscissa x and the ordinate y are found by projecting the point onto the axes.
    \n ‚ó¶ Distance Formula: The distance between two points M‚ÇÅ(x‚ÇÅ, y‚ÇÅ) and M‚ÇÇ(x‚ÇÇ, y‚ÇÇ) is given by the formula: |M‚ÇÅM‚ÇÇ| = ‚àö((x‚ÇÇ - x‚ÇÅ)¬≤ + (y‚ÇÇ - y‚ÇÅ)¬≤).
</string>
    <string name="SectionThreeTheoryProperties_3">!!! Empty !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionThreeTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionThreeQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionFourTheoryDef_3">‚Ä¢ Power Operation Rules:
    \n ‚Ä¢ (1) Multiplying powers with the same base: Add the exponents: a·µê ¬∑ a‚Åø = a·µê‚Å∫‚Åø.
\n ‚Ä¢ (2) Dividing powers with the same base: Subtract the exponents: a·µê / a‚Åø = a·µê‚Åª‚Åø (for m > n).
\n ‚Ä¢ (3) Raising a power to a power: Multiply the exponents: (a·µê)‚Åø = a·µê‚Åø.
\n ‚Ä¢ (4) Power of a negative number: (-a)‚Åø is a‚Åø if n is even, and -a‚Åø if n is odd.
\n ‚Ä¢ (5) Raising a product to a power: Distribute the exponent: (ab)‚Åø = a‚Åøb‚Åø.
\n ‚Ä¢ (6) Raising a fraction to a power: Distribute the exponent to the numerator and denominator: (a/b)‚Åø = a‚Åø / b‚Åø (for b ‚âÝ 0).

</string>
    <string name="SectionFourTheoryProperties_3">!!! Empty !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionFourTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionFourQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionFiveTheoryDef_3">‚Ä¢ Definition: The arithmetical square root of a non-negative number a is a non-negative number b such that b¬≤ = a. It is denoted ‚àöa = b. The expression ‚àöa is called the radicand.
\n ‚Ä¢ Uniqueness: For any real number a ‚â• 0, it is possible to take only one arithmetical square root.
\n ‚Ä¢ Key Identity: For any real number a, ‚àöa¬≤ = |a|.
</string>
    <string name="SectionFiveTheoryProperties_3">‚Ä¢ Properties of Arithmetical Square Roots (for a ‚â• 0, b > 0):
    \n 1. Root of a product: ‚àöab = ‚àöa ¬∑ ‚àöb.
    \n 2. Root of a fraction: ‚àö(a/b) = ‚àöa / ‚àöb.
    \n 3. Comparison: If a > b > 0, then ‚àöa > ‚àöb.
\n ‚Ä¢ Transformations:
    \n 1. Removing a factor from the radicand: ‚àöa¬≤b = |a|‚àöb.
    \n 2. Bringing a factor into the radicand: a‚àöb = ‚àöa¬≤b (for a ‚â• 0).</string>
    <string name="SectionFiveTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionFiveQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionSixTheoryDef_3">Definitions:
    \n ‚ó¶ Zero exponent: For any a ‚âÝ 0, a‚Å∞ = 1. The expression 0‚Å∞ has no sense.
    \n ‚ó¶ Negative exponent: For a ‚âÝ 0 and a natural number n, a‚Åª‚Åø = 1 / a‚Åø. The expression 0‚Åª‚Åø has no sense.
</string>
    <string name="SectionSixTheoryProperties_3">Properties: The properties of powers with natural exponents (listed in Sec. 4.4) hold true for any integer exponents p and q:
    \n 1. a·µñ ¬∑ a‚Åπ = a·µñ‚Å∫‚Åπ
    \n 2. (a·µñ)‚Åπ = a·µñ‚Åπ
    \n 3. a·µñ / a‚Åπ = a·µñ‚Åª‚Åπ
    \n 4. (ab)·µñ = a·µñb·µñ
    \n 5. (a/b)·µñ = a·µñ / b·µñ</string>
    <string name="SectionSixTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionSixQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionSevenTheoryDef_3">‚Ä¢ Definition: For a real number a ‚â• 0 and a natural number n ‚â• 2, the arithmetical nth root, ‚Åø‚àöa, is the non-negative number b such that b‚Åø = a. The expression ‚Åø‚àöa only has sense for a ‚â• 0.
‚Ä¢ Basic Rules for Operations with Arithmetical Roots (for a ‚â• 0, b > 0):
    1. Changing the index: The value is unchanged if the index and the exponent of the radicand are multiplied by the same natural number k: ‚Åø‚àöa = ‚Åø·µè‚àöa·µè.
    2. Multiplying roots: ‚Åø‚àöa ¬∑ ‚Åø‚àöb = ‚Åø‚àöab.
    3. Dividing roots: ‚Åø‚àöa / ‚Åø‚àöb = ‚Åø‚àö(a/b).
    4. Raising a root to a power: (‚Åø‚àöa)·µê = ‚Åø‚àöa·µê.
    5. Taking the root of a root: ·µê‚àö‚Åø‚àöa = ·µê‚Åø‚àöa.
‚Ä¢ Like Roots: Roots are considered like (or similar) if their radicands and indices are equal. Simplification of sums and differences is only possible for like roots.
‚Ä¢ Key Identity: The identity ‚Åø‚àöa‚Åø = |a| holds if n is an even number; ‚Åø‚àöa‚Åø = a if n is an odd number.
</string>
    <string name="SectionSevenTheoryProperties_3"> !!! Empty !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionSevenTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionSevenQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionEightTheoryDef_3">Definition: If a > 0 and x is a rational number p/q (where p is an integer and q is a natural number ‚â• 2), then aÀ£ = a^(p/q) = ‚Åπ‚àöa·µñ. \n
        Special Cases: If a = 0 and x > 0, then aÀ£ = 0.

</string>
    <string name="SectionEightTheoryProperties_3"> The properties of powers with integral exponents also extend to powers with any rational exponent and a positive base. </string>
    <string name="SectionEightTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionEightQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionNineTheoryDef_3">Notion of a Power with an Irrational Exponent: The value of aÀ£ where x is irrational is defined via sequences of decimal approximations. For a > 0, this process yields a unique number. The definition a‚ÅªÀ£ = 1/aÀ£ also holds for a positive irrational number x.
</string>
    <string name="SectionNineTheoryProperties_3"> The Properties of Powers with a Real Exponent are represented by the fact that, for any real numbers x and y and admissible a and b, we have that:
    \n 1. aÀ£ ¬∑ a ∏ = aÀ£‚Å∫ ∏
    \n 2. (aÀ£) ∏ = aÀ£ ∏
    \n 3. aÀ£ / a ∏ = aÀ£‚Åª ∏
    \n 4. (ab)À£ = aÀ£bÀ£
    \n 5. (a/b)À£ = aÀ£ / bÀ£ </string>
    <string name="SectionNineTheoryWorkedExamples_3">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionNineQuiz_3">!!! Solve the quiz !!!</string>
</resources>