<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name_16">License_Project_2</string>

    <string name="SectionOneTheoryDef_16">• Parallel Lines: Two straight lines in space that lie in one plane and have no common points.
• Skew Lines: Two straight lines in space that do not lie in one plane.
• Angle Between Skew Lines: The angle between intersecting lines that are respectively parallel to the given skew lines.
• Perpendicular Line to a Plane: A straight line cutting a plane that is perpendicular to any straight line lying in that plane.
• Distance Between Parallel Planes: The length of the segment cut off by the planes on any common perpendicular.</string>
    <string name="SectionOneTheoryProperties_16">• Perpendicularity Test (Theorem 1): If a straight line cutting a plane is perpendicular to two intersecting lines in that plane, it is perpendicular to the entire plane.
• Parallelism of Planes (Theorem 3): If two intersecting lines of one plane are respectively parallel to two intersecting lines of another plane, the planes are parallel.
• Plane Separation: Parallel planes are equidistant; any perpendicular segment between them is congruent (e.g., ∣A1A2∣=∣B1B2∣).
• Angle of Line/Plane: The angle between a line and its projection onto the plane.</string>
    <string name="SectionOneTheoryWorkedExamples_16">• Problem 1 (Angle Between Skew Lines): Find the angle between diagonals of adjacent faces of a cube. By drawing a line parallel to one diagonal to intersect the other, an equilateral triangle is formed, proving the angle is 60∘.
• Problem 2 (Mutual Perpendiculars): Construction of three mutually perpendicular lines a,b, and c. By establishing line OA perpendicular to plane α (containing a,b) and line OD perpendicular to OB, the three axes are proven perpendicular via Theorem 1.</string>
    <string name="SectionOneQuiz_16">!!! Solve the Quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionTwoTheoryDef_16">• Polyhedron: A solid bounded by plane polygons called faces; intersections of faces are edges, and intersections of edges are vertices.
• Right Prism: A polyhedron whose bases are parallel congruent polygons and whose lateral edges are perpendicular to the bases.
• Rectangular Parallelepiped: A right prism whose base is a rectangle.
• Cube: A rectangular parallelepiped where all twelve edges are equal.
• Pyramid: A polyhedron consisting of a polygon (base) and a vertex not in the base plane, joined by triangular lateral faces.
• Regular Pyramid: A pyramid with a regular polygon base whose vertex projects onto the centre of the base.</string>
    <string name="SectionTwoTheoryProperties_16">• Prism Area: Lateral area S_lat=Ph (perimeter × altitude); Total area S=S_lat+2S_base.
• Parallelepiped Diagonal: The square of any diagonal is equal to the sum of the squares of its three dimensions (d^2=a^2+b^2+c^2).
• Volume: For a parallelepiped V=abc; for any right prism V=Sh.
• Pyramid Area/Volume: Lateral area of a regular pyramid is S_lat=(P*h_lat)/2 (where h_lat is slant height); Volume of any pyramid is V=(S_base*h)/3.</string>
    <string name="SectionTwoTheoryWorkedExamples_16">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionTwoQuiz_16">!!! Solve the Quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionThreeTheoryDef_16">• Cylinder: A solid generated by line segments (elements) perpendicular to two parallel planes and bounded by congruent circles.
\n • Cone: A solid generated by joining all points of a circle to a vertex S; the line from the vertex to the base center is the axis.
\n • Sphere: All points in space at a distance not exceeding R from a center O; its boundary is the sphere.</string>
    <string name="SectionThreeTheoryProperties_16">!!! EMPTY !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionThreeTheoryWorkedExamples_16">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionThreeQuiz_16">!!! Solve the Quiz !!!</string>

    <string name="SectionFourTheoryDef_16">!!! EMPTY !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionFourTheoryProperties_16">!!! EMPTY !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionFourTheoryWorkedExamples_16">!!! Worked Examples !!!</string>
    <string name="SectionFourQuiz_16">!!! Solve the Quiz !!!</string>
</resources>